我生过一个孩子
I had a child once.
看他这样子  比我连生四个都疼
I'd rather have four more than do what he's trying to do.
忍着点  罗比
Hang in there, Robbie.
罗比一直有很严重的心动过速
Robbie's been having fairly sustained runs of v-tach.
贝利医生安排马上给他心梗测试板试验和心电图
Dr. Bailey ordered a cardiac panel and a stat EKG.
罗比  你只是感觉胃疼
Robbie, is the pain just in your stomach,
还是胸也疼
or does your chest hurt, too?
胸
Chest.
索他洛尔：Ⅲ类抗心律失常药物给他注射80毫克的索他洛尔和6毫克吗啡
Get me 80 milligrams I.V. Sotalol and 6 of Morphine.
好的  医生
Yes, doctor.
罗比  我要你
Robbie, I'm
试着深呼吸
going to need you to take some deep breaths.
疼死了
It hurts.
我知道
I know.
束支传导阻滞容易再次诱发心动过速
Bundle branch block re-entrant v-tach.
他有可能突发心脏病
He's at risk for sudden cardio attack?